http://lifelinecelltech.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Save 20% on Lung and Airway Cells. Use "Lung1220" to order online by December 20. (US Customers only). Click here!
During the course of our relationship with our customers over the Lifeline® or International Stem Cell websites, we may collect certain information that is required for us to communicate with our customers and to provide superior service to our customers. This information is collected when our customers call us or visit our website or purchase products over our website. This information consists of personal information that our customers provide such as e-mail address, mailing address, products purchased and the technical questions asked.
By using this site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
We take efforts to keep your information private and the following Privacy Policy explains how we use the information. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to websites that are outside of the Lifeline® or International Stem Cell website.
This site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect information from site visitors in this age group. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose to Web sites.
Passive information collected and uses for passive information
As you navigate the website, certain anonymous information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies. Your Internet browser automatically transmits to this site some of this anonymous information, such as the URL of the Web site you just came from and the Internet Protocol (IP) address and the browser version your computer is currently using. We use this Passive Information in the following manners:
To gather statistical information used to improve product performance.
To gather market research information to provide new products or services.
To track purchase history information.
To improve this website.
To notify our customers (with their permission) of new products and services.
We may allow third-party vendors, including Google, to use a cookie to serve ads to you based on your past visits to our website. You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ads Settings.  Alternately, you can  opt out of  third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
Personally identifiable information
If you provide personally identifiable information to this site, we may combine such information with other actively collected information unless we specify otherwise at the point of collection. Lifeline® does not disclose personal information to third parties, except in the following instances. When permission has been explicitly granted by the offering individual. When a sub-contractor who has concluded a non-disclosure agreement with our company beforehand is consigned personal information in part or in entirety in a range necessary for achieving the intended purpose. When it is required by a court of law, etc. When disclosed so that personal identification is not possible. When personal information is consigned to a third party, appropriate supervision implemented through contractual obligation, etc. ensures that there is no leakage or re-offering of the entrusted information.
Handling of personally identifiable information
Personal information gathered on the Lifeline® or International Stem Cell site will be handled according to the use specified, disclosed or notified to you, or according to the permission granted by you. Personal Information may also be used when it is necessary to contact you directly.
Lifeline® will never sell or rent your information to other marketers.
Lifeline® will take reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information as you transmit your information from your computer to our site and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Moreover, where you use passwords, ID numbers, or other special access features on this site, it is your responsibility to safeguard them.
REVISIONS
Lifeline® Cell Technology may revise or withdraw the Content, in whole or in part, at any time without notice. Lifeline® Cell Technology may at any time revise these Web Site Terms of Use by updating this posting. By using the Site, you agree to be bound by any such revisions and you agree to periodically visit this page to determine the then current Web Site Terms of Use to which you are bound.
Contacts Regarding Personal Information
Please call (301) 845-7787 with any questions regarding personal information.
ACCEPTANCE OF CONTRACT TERMS JURISDICTION
In exchange for accessing, browsing and/or using the Site, you agree to be bound by these terms and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations, including without limitation U.S. export and re-export control laws and regulations. You represent you have the legal authority to accept these Web Site Terms of Use on behalf of yourself or any party you represent. If any provision of these Web Site Terms of Use is held to be invalid by any law, rule, order or regulation of any governmental entity or by the final determination of any state or federal court, such invalidity shall not affect the enforceability of any other provision of the Web Site Terms of Use.
If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use this site.
The Site is controlled and operated in whole or in part by Lifeline® Cell Technology from its offices within the United States. BY ACCESSING THE SITE YOU AGREE THAT THE STATUTES AND LAWS OF THE UNITED STATES AND THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA, U.S.A., WITHOUT REGARD TO CONFLICTS OF LAWS PRINCIPLES, WILL APPLY TO ALL MATTERS RELATING TO USE OF THE SITE, AND YOU AGREE THAT ANY LITIGATION SHALL BE SUBJECT TO THE EXCLUSIVE JURISDICTION OF THE STATE OR FEDERAL COURTS IN LOS ANGELES, CALIFORNIA, U.S.A. Those who access the Site from other locations do so at their own risk and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. Lifeline® Cell Technology makes no representation that the Content in the Site is appropriate or available for use in other locations, and access to it from territories where the Content is illegal is prohibited. You acknowledge that Lifeline® Cell Technology reserves the right in its sole discretion to refuse or terminate access to the Site by you at any time.
USE OF CONTENT
This Site is © COPYRIGHT 2007-2019 Lifeline® Cell Technology Corporation. All Rights Reserved.
While Lifeline Cell Technology provides the information on this server to anyone, we retain copyright on all copyrightable aspects of the Site. You acknowledge, that you have been advised by Lifeline® Cell Technology that the Content is protected in the U.S. and internationally by a variety of laws, including but not limited to, copyright laws and treaty provisions, trademark laws and other proprietary rights laws (collectively “Rights”). In addition to Lifeline® Cell Technology’s Rights in individual elements of the Content, Lifeline® Cell Technology and/or its licensors own a copyright in the selection, coordination and arrangement of the Content.
You are hereby granted permission to access the Content from the Site in whole or in part, (and, except where otherwise specified by Lifeline® Cell Technology, print a single copy of the information for your own personal use), but only for purposes of viewing and browsing through the Site. You are also hereby granted permission to store the files on your computer for your own personal use. However, these permissions terminate automatically if you breach any of the Web Site Terms of Use. Lifeline® Cell Technology is not granting you any permission to use the Content other than the permission expressly stated in these Web Site Terms of Use. All other use of Content from the Site, including, but not limited to modification, publication, transmission, participation in the transfer or sale of, reproduction, creation of derivative works from, distribution, performance, display, incorporation into another web site, reproducing the Site (whether by linking, framing or any other method), “mirroring” the Site or in any other way exploiting any of the Content, in whole or in part, or downloading and using software repeatedly for uses other than those expressly permitted, may not be made without Lifeline® Cell Technology’s prior express written consent.
TRADEMARKS AND SERVICE MARKS
The word-mark LIFELINE® CELL TECHNOLOGY is owned by Lifeline® Cell Technology and is registered with the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office. Other marks, such as product and service names, found on Lifeline® Cell Technology web sites are owned by Lifeline® Cell Technology or by their respective owners. No Lifeline® Cell Technology trademark or service mark may be used as a hyperlink without prior written permission. Your use of Lifeline® Cell Technology’s trademarks in advertising and the promotion of Lifeline Cell Technology’s products and services requires Lifeline® Cell Technology’s prior written consent and requires an accompanying statement that the trademarks belong to Lifeline® Cell Technology.
SUBMISSIONS OF INFORMATION
Lifeline® Cell Technology does not guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Site. You agree to assume the security risk for any information you provide using the Site. Any Personally Identifiable Information shall be handled under the self-imposed rules outlined in this web site.
Do not send any confidential or proprietary information to Lifeline® Cell Technology through the Site that is not Personally Identifiable Information. Any information you do send to Lifeline® Cell Technology through the Site will be deemed NOT to be confidential. For any information you do send, you hereby grant Lifeline® Cell Technology an unrestricted, royalty-free, irrevocable license to use, reproduce, display, perform, modify, transmit and distribute the information, and agree that Lifeline® Cell Technology is similarly licensed to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques that you send Lifeline® Cell Technology for any purpose, without compensation to you.
You are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from the Site any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic, or profane material, or any other material that could give rise to any civil or criminal liability under the law.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY
LIFELINE® CELL TECHNOLOGY DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE, VALIDITY, ACCURACY, OR RELIABILITY OF, OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF, OR OTHERWISE RESPECTING, THE CONTENT OF THE SITE OR ANY OTHER WEB SITES LINKED TO OR FROM THE SITE. THE CONTENT OF THE SITE IS PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT POSSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, LIFELINE® CELL TECHNOLOGY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT OR OTHER VIOLATION OF RIGHTS.
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR LIMITATION ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY LASTS, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS OR EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY.
You may not rely upon the information contained in the web site for any commercial decision. If you are considering licensing any product or service provided by Lifeline® Cell Technology or a competitor, please contact Lifeline® Cell Technology or the competitor for updated information specific to your needs. Further, Lifeline® Cell Technology will be not be liable for any representation, warranty or covenant unless set forth in a binding contract with Lifeline® Cell Technology executed by responsible officers of both parties to that contract.
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEB SITES
Lifeline® Cell Technology makes no representations whatsoever about any other web site which you may access through the Site. When you access a non-Lifeline® Cell Technology web site, please understand that it is independent from Lifeline® Cell Technology, and that Lifeline® Cell Technology has no control over the content on that web site. In addition, a link to a non-Lifeline® Cell Technology web site does not mean that Lifeline® Cell Technology endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content, or the use, of such web site. It is up to you to take precautions to ensure that whatever you select for your use is free of such items as viruses, worms, trojan horses and other items of a destructive nature. Lifeline® Cell Technology makes no representation or warranty as to any third party products. Note also that Lifeline® Cell Technology’s Privacy Policy does not apply to any non-Lifeline® Cell Technology web site which may be accessed through the Lifeline® Cell Technology site. Please refer to such non-Lifeline® Cell Technology web sites’ own privacy policies (if any) to determine the privacy policies which apply when using such non-Lifeline® Cell Technology web sites.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
LIFELINE® CELL TECHNOLOGY WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE USE OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE SITE, ITS CONTENT OR LINKS, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
FORWARD LOOKING STATEMENTS
Any statements herein that are forward-looking are made pursuant to the safe harbor provisions of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. You are cautioned that forward-looking statements involve risks and uncertainties which may affect business prospects and performance. Actual results may differ materially from the results predicted, and reported results should not be considered an indication of future performance. Potential risks and uncertainties may include economic, competitive, governmental, technological, or other factors.
Contact us
Shop By Product
Cells
Endothelial
Epithelial
Fibroblasts
Hematopoietic
iPS Validated Fibroblasts
Reproductive (Male)
Reproductive (Female)
Material Safety Data Sheets (SDS)
